Ayona Das SOFTWARE ENGINEER

(+91)-9163157008 Ayona3099@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Currently working as a **Software Engineer** at **Infinite Computer Solution** with **2 years of experience** in **JavaScript automated test frameworks**. Passionate about delivering beautiful user experiences using scripts. Always open to challenges and to learn new technologies, tools or frameworks if needed.

SKILLS

Front-end JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap

Programming-Language Java **Database** SQL

Others Git, Github, AGILE, Unit Testing

Soft Skills Problem Solving, Communication, Attention to Detail, Creativity, Collaborative

Work History

Software Engineer (Workflow Automation)

Aug 2022 — Present

Infinite Computer Solutions

Gurugram, IN

- Designed and developed more than 20 scripts to save over 50,000 customers time and developed screens for the loan mortgage team.
- · Worked individually in the team on critical scripts and made technical documentation for the clients.
- Technology used: JAVASCRIPT, HTML, CSS Logical thinking, Bugs fixing, Scripting, Sagent Loanserv automated tools.
- Reviewed and provided comprehensive feedback on 50+ Pull Requests, ensuring adherence to coding standards & optimizing code efficiency.

AMORTIZATION CALCULATOR

- · Developed a highly efficient **calculator** for clients to calculate the loan mortgage and display graphs, pie charts, and table data.
- This calculator has a feature to export the .csv file of table data which will be easier for clients to calculate further.
- This project has been nominated for **Ignite** and will used by more than 250+customers.
- · Technologies used: HTML, CSS and JavaScript, Automation, Scripting

Automation Engineer(Internship)

Jan 2022 — July 2022

Ericsson

Noida,IN

- · Developed an automation Solution that identifies and resolves system outages and performance issues.
- · Developed an automation solution that monitors system performance and proactively identifies and resolves potential issues.
- · Technology used: java, Groovy, automated tools

EDUCATION

B.E-Computer Science and Engineering, Chandigarh University

Jun 2018 — Jun 2022

CGPA: 7.45/10.00

ACTIVITIES & ACHIEVEMENTS

- · Completed 30 days program of Google Cloud (self-paced labs)
- · Certifications of Introduction to Java Programming (NPTEL)
- · Certifications of AWS Fundamentals: Cloud-Native (Coursera)
- · Got 2 Spark award
- · Hosted Hackathons and technical events as a Tech-Org Lead at the Computer Society of India Student Chapter.